<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
<row Id="686910" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:04:36.063" Score="1" ViewCount="853" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a UITableView added in InterfaceBuilder. My app runs in LandScape. Because I was unable to use autorotation (still can't figure that out). I am using Transforming it for now. Having said that, I now have to place the UITableView in some weird position for it to look correct after transformation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My table is fine but I cannot reach to the last couple of rows in the table. It almost seems like its Cut Off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What settings would be causing this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks very much in advance&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="KenW" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:28:41.450" Title="Cannot see the last row in my UiTableView" Tags="&lt;iphone&gt;&lt;uitableview&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686911" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686822" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:04:48.793" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can paint graphics into your own off-screen image in another thread and copy to the screen in the EDT. But for single threaded stuff, I would hope your frame rate is high enough to be able to do it in the EDT.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4725" OwnerDisplayName="Tom Hawtin - tackline" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:04:48.793" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="686913" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686857" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:04:58.603" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you don't link against it, you are in the clear. So instead of developing an API for this open-source command line tool, just write a little wrapper that interacts with the program directly on the command line.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since you are not linking, and now are just executing a binary your code will not have to be released under the GPL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You may use fork, pipe, exec and friends to do this! It is a simple solution and depending on how the application expects its input on the command line it can work very well (curses based stuff is harder ... need a terminal of some sort)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the comments it sounds like even this is not valid, and could still cause issues. I suggest contacting a lawyer to make sure you are in the clear, he will be able to interpret the GPL and tell you what you may and may not do with GPL'ed code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would think that just executing an GPL'ed program and then sending it data (a.l.a. piping data into it) should not cause your program to also be GPL'ed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the GPL is too complex, if I use a command line tool by executing it and piping data to it my program can still become GPL. That is just weird. Give me BSD, and or MIT anytime of day, way simpler to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="13986" OwnerDisplayName="X-Istence" LastEditorUserId="13986" LastEditorDisplayName="X-Istence" LastEditDate="2009-03-26T23:44:46.150" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T23:44:46.150" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="686914" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686857" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:05.657" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;With GPL I think the only way out is to wrap it in something like a COM object (which would also need to be GPL or compatabile), and connect to the object at runtime. Since this keeps you from (staticly) linking with GPL code, you'd be off the hook.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That trick will work with GPL v2 code, but may not work with GPL v3.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29639" LastEditorUserId="29639" LastEditDate="2009-03-27T14:42:09.613" LastActivityDate="2009-03-27T14:42:09.613" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="686915" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="184618" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:09.430" Score="16" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// A Gorgon class - For the love of Zeus don't look directly at it!&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="7862" OwnerDisplayName="itsmatt" LastEditorUserId="6148" LastEditorDisplayName="Trey Jackson" LastEditDate="2009-04-01T17:34:20.113" LastActivityDate="2009-04-01T17:34:20.113" CommentCount="0" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-26T18:05:09.430" />
<row Id="686916" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="216779" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:16.450" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Axis2 does not support Spring web services when using Jax-WS. See this mailing list post: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://markmail.org/message/hohdmsupo3r3gltl?q=list:org%2Eapache%2Ews%2Eaxis-user+spring+jax-ws&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://markmail.org/message/hohdmsupo3r3gltl?q=list:org%2Eapache%2Ews%2Eaxis-user+spring+jax-ws&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do this you will need a custom module to add a BeanFactory into the MessageContext and then retrieve it out in your web service. Or you might write a custom dispatcher. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="28946" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:05:16.450" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686918" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="680200" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:43.627" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you can, I'd recommend writing to the EventLog and creating rules in SCOM to monitor. We use this extensively and it works well, even to a point of putting together pieces of code which monitor certain elements of our apps and writing values to the event log, where SCOM parses for the errors, and graphs those, plus informational errors, into reports showing stats over a given time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am however quite keen on rewriting some that into WMI, and having SCOM poll the WMI service for those same counters, as writing queue lengths to event log every 15 minutes seems a little wasteful ;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="83260" OwnerDisplayName="Paul Stevens" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:05:43.627" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="686919" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686905" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:45.763" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;You get your browser's language for your button. There's no way to change it programmatically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="76583" OwnerDisplayName="Seb" LastEditorUserId="63550" LastEditDate="2010-01-21T19:22:49.687" LastActivityDate="2010-01-21T19:22:49.687" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="686920" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686216" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:05:49.757" Score="2" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Do&#xA;&#xA; love();&#xA;&#xA; honor();&#xA;&#xA; cherish();&#xA;&#xA;Loop Until (tiffany.age &amp;gt;= 49 or tiffany.trustfund &amp;lt; 0 or smokingHotOfficeBabe.hookups &amp;gt; 0 )&#xA;&#xA;if (smokingHotOfficeBabe.hookups &amp;gt; 0) return TotalAssets / 2&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sorry, could not resist.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="79856" OwnerDisplayName="Jordan" LastEditorUserId="5640" LastEditorDisplayName="Rich B" LastEditDate="2009-03-26T18:13:29.660" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:13:29.660" CommentCount="0" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-26T18:05:49.727" />
<row Id="686923" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="686992" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:09.583" Score="2" ViewCount="1651" Body="&lt;p&gt;Usually not calling Dispose indicates a possible error or sloppy code and may lead to some hard to find bugs.  Ideally I would like to spot if Disposed was not called during unit tests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the methods we used was to put Debug.Assert in the Finalizer&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#if DEBUG&#xA;~MyClass()&#xA;{&#xA;    Debug.Assert(false, “MyClass.Dispose() was not called”);&#xA;}&#xA;#endif&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And we found ourselves clicking through assert message boxes but it didn’t work well with continuous integration builds that would ignore the popups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14074" LastEditorUserId="14074" LastEditDate="2009-03-27T14:23:59.610" LastActivityDate="2009-03-27T19:00:54.797" Title="How to make sure that Dispose method was called on IDisposable object and if possible to integrate it into continuous integration?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;unit-testing&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="0" />
<row Id="686924" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="686935" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:09.990" Score="0" ViewCount="1456" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is a snippet from my &lt;code&gt;index.php&lt;/code&gt; page, where I'm displaying a menu with three HTML links. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Selecting a menu item defines the page parameter, which the PHP templating logic then loads, populating into &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;main&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;span-24&quot; id=&quot;menu&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;td&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;index.php?page=races&quot;&amp;gt;Races&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;td&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;index.php?page=runners&quot;&amp;gt;Runners&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;&#xA;      &amp;lt;td&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;index.php?page=searchRunners&quot;&amp;gt;Search&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;lt;!-- main content --&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;span-24&quot; id=&quot;main&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;?php &#xA;  $MYROOT=$_SERVER['DOCUMENT_ROOT'];&#xA;  if(isset($_GET['page']))&#xA;  {&#xA;    $page=$_GET['page'];&#xA;    @ require_once($MYROOT.&quot;/$page.php&quot;);&#xA;  }&#xA;  else&#xA;  {&#xA;    @ require_once($MYROOT.&quot;/races.php&quot;);&#xA;  }&#xA;?&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This solution works fine, but I'm worried that as I add more pages and have more page parameters to track, this approach will become difficult to maintain with the various PHP &lt;code&gt;require()&lt;/code&gt; / &lt;code&gt;require_once()&lt;/code&gt; method calls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also have jQuery available and I was wondering what could be the benefits or drawbacks of just using a AJAX based query to render the HTML for &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;main&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think using AJAX might be a better solution, since I'll have more flexibility in the page that I can call and which parameters I can pass within the AJAX call.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know PHP and the AJAX can be used together, but if you were starting this type of project, how would you do it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="55794" LastEditorUserId="18771" LastEditorDisplayName="Tomalak" LastEditDate="2009-03-26T18:26:35.433" LastActivityDate="2009-05-05T03:31:08.060" Title="To use PHP templates or jQuery AJAX calls?" Tags="&lt;php&gt;&lt;jquery&gt;&lt;ajax&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="686925" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686896" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:21.160" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think the common concensus would be use a custom return code (integer).  As long as the service documents what the possible return codes are, this should be feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54420" OwnerDisplayName="Josh Stodola" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:06:21.160" CommentCount="5" />
<row Id="686926" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686897" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:36.963" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can use the usual &lt;code&gt;acquire; try { use; } finally { release; }&lt;/code&gt;. Alternatively you can abstract the resource handling with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/341971/what-is-the-execute-around-idiom&quot;&gt;Execute Around idiom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4725" OwnerDisplayName="Tom Hawtin - tackline" LastEditorUserId="13531" LastEditorDisplayName="mmyers" LastEditDate="2009-03-26T20:03:02.970" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T20:03:02.970" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686927" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686896" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:40.160" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I return a small class called ResultSet from each WebMethod, which contains an int errorcode and a string errormessage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This gives you an easy check for error/success, and some details if things go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the WebMethod needs to return data, I'll inherit from ResultSet to give a specific ResultSet to include the data as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="19032" OwnerDisplayName="Moose" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:06:40.160" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="686929" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="686957" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:06:54.793" Score="2" ViewCount="476" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there any documentation on exactly how expensive it is:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if (x.IsInvokeRequired)&#xA;{&#xA;    beginInvoke . . . .&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you have a case where 90% of the time is on a background thread (and thus required) is it worth it?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you have a case where 90% of the time is on a UI thread (and thus not required) is it worth it?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any metrics around this would be great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4653" OwnerDisplayName="mek" LastEditorUserId="496830" LastEditDate="2011-11-17T18:04:26.563" LastActivityDate="2011-11-17T18:04:26.563" Title="How expensive is the IsInvokeRequired" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;multithreading&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686930" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="683132" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:07:02.313" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;You should detect the &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms647592.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;WM_CONTEXTMENU&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; windows message by &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/2e1ew1ek.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;specifying a handler in your message map&lt;/a&gt;. In the handler you can then show the context menu. You then need to make sure you also handle the menu commands in your message map for when a command is selected from the context menu. Use the &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/xsxbs7hc.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;COMMAND_HANDLER&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; macro in your message map for this part.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23234" OwnerDisplayName="Jeff Yates" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:07:02.313" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686931" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="687622" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:07:07.773" Score="7" ViewCount="6067" Body="&lt;p&gt;If curly brackets ('{' and '}') are used in Lua, what are they used for?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="43496" OwnerDisplayName="Sydius" LastActivityDate="2009-04-06T12:22:11.780" Title="Are curly brackets used in Lua?" Tags="&lt;syntax&gt;&lt;lua&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="3" />
<row Id="686932" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686611" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:07:19.440" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure if you can use it &lt;em&gt;from&lt;/em&gt; Eclipse, but nothing stops you from just &lt;em&gt;using&lt;/em&gt; it. From cmd / xterm / whatever. It's not going to interfere with Eclipse in anyway, nor will it interfere with Subclipse (which I'm assuming is what you're using).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1666" OwnerDisplayName="SCdF" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:07:19.440" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686934" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:25.273" Score="2" ViewCount="2059" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm using Perl's File::Find module to scan for files, directories, and links.  Among other things, I want the utility I'm writing to report dangling links.  In theory, this is supported by creating a subroutine to be called whenever an dangling link has been found, and calling the find method with a hash reference of appropriate values, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;my %options = (&#xA;   wanted            =&amp;gt; \&amp;amp;ProcessFile,&#xA;   follow            =&amp;gt; 1,&#xA;   follow_skip       =&amp;gt; 2,&#xA;   dangling_symlinks =&amp;gt; \&amp;amp;Dangling&#xA;);&#xA;&#xA;find(\%options, @ARGV);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite deliberately creating a dangling link to test this, File::Find never, ever calls the subroutine &quot;Dangling&quot;.  Everything else works except this feature (i.e. the ProcessFile sub gets called as expected, links are followed, etc..  Anyone have andy experience with this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="34903" LastEditorUserId="2766176" LastEditorDisplayName="brian d foy" LastEditDate="2009-03-27T12:58:08.490" LastActivityDate="2009-03-27T12:58:08.490" Title="Why doesn't File::Find handle my dangling symlink?" Tags="&lt;perl&gt;&lt;symlink&gt;&lt;dangling&gt;&lt;file-find&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="686935" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686924" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:28.377" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;You don't want to do this. AJAX is nice and all but this would be misusing it. It would not only needlessly make the website inaccessible to people with Javascript disabled (which I'm sure you're aware of), it would also kill the navigational standard of the web on your website. How could someone send a link to a friend to check out the Races page, then? How can I go back and forth between pages? There's workarounds to this, but it is not worth it. You are better suited to just re-factor your PHP code so it is dynamic while safe in including what you want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16417" OwnerDisplayName="Paolo Bergantino" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:08:28.377" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686936" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686931" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:32.200" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;list/ditionary constructor (i.e. table type constructor). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They are not used for code blocks if that's what you mean.  For that Lua just uses the end keyword to end the block. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://merd.sourceforge.net/pixel/language-study/syntax-across-languages-per-language/Lua.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;See here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3153" OwnerDisplayName="Brian R. Bondy" LastEditorUserId="3153" LastEditorDisplayName="Brian R. Bondy" LastEditDate="2009-03-27T10:10:14.620" LastActivityDate="2009-03-27T10:10:14.620" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="686937" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686724" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:33.650" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;Simple answer - whenever your SQL is not altering data, and you have a query that might interfere with other activity (via locking).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's worth considering for any queries used for reports, especially if the query takes more than, say, 1 second.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's especially useful if you have OLAP-type reports you're running against an OLTP database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thefirst question to ask, though, is &quot;why am I worrying about this?&quot; ln my experience, fudging the default locking behavior often takes place when someone is in &quot;try anything&quot; mode and this is one case where unexpected consequences are not unlikely.  Too often it's a case of premature optimization and can too easily get left embedded in an application &quot;just in case.&quot; It's important to understand why you're doing it, what problem it solves, and whether you actually have the problem. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31641" OwnerDisplayName="le dorfier" LastEditorUserId="31641" LastEditDate="2015-07-17T15:27:22.333" LastActivityDate="2015-07-17T15:27:22.333" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="686938" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="686216" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:50.123" Score="9" Body="&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// Java-ish pseudocode&#xA;public Happiness marriage(husband, wife) {&#xA;  while (true) {&#xA;    husband.love(wife);&#xA;    wife.love(husband);&#xA;    if (bedrooms.size() &amp;gt; family.size() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; savings &amp;gt; 0) {&#xA;       newChild = fork();&#xA;       family.add(newChild);&#xA;       savings = 0;&#xA;    }&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="78743" OwnerDisplayName="jiggy" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:08:50.123" CommentCount="3" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-03-26T18:08:50.110" />
<row Id="686940" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="211971" CreationDate="2009-03-26T18:08:56.363" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Thanks for that last tip Sam. I had a dialog which opened, meaning my grid lost focus every time the dialog closed. I use this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if(currentRow &amp;gt;= 0 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; currentRow &amp;lt; lstGrid.Items.Count) {&#xA;    lstGrid.SelectedIndex = currentRow;&#xA;    lstGrid.ScrollIntoView(lstGrid.SelectedItem);&#xA;    if(shouldFocusGrid) {&#xA;        ListViewItem item = lstGrid.ItemContainerGenerator.ContainerFromItem(lstGrid.SelectedItem) as ListViewItem;&#xA;        item.Focus();&#xA;    }&#xA;} else if(shouldFocusGrid) {&#xA;    lstGrid.Focus();&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="30512" OwnerDisplayName="Echilon" LastActivityDate="2009-03-26T18:08:56.363" CommentCount="0" />
</posts>